{
    "id": "c9e9150f1e6f494f9fa7663f9a7e2f2f",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The publishers are planning to bring ………………. a new edition of this book soon.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "up",
                "out",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "459bedfc7d794cd788870633f510dd41"
        },
        {
            "question": "This scheme will eventually fall ………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "in",
                "through",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1cc9049d819a45db8d615a2c26f8795f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I can’t get on ………………….. her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9e984c09383b44718da0b9ecd6b9c055"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am looking ………………… to being a grandmother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "after",
                "toward",
                "forward"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "41c192e3655a497aab5caee876b6b862"
        },
        {
            "question": "When he became a celebrity he began to look down ………………… his old friends.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "upon",
                "at",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "49f7b15c61a94cb5934352a95d5058fe"
        },
        {
            "question": "The chief guest gave .....................… the prizes.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "out",
                "in",
                "away"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "69f9225d3c864cef9652a48374a6b8f6"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you don’t understand the meaning of a word, you should look it …………………. in the dictionary.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "up",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "181592e9f15b44e69d8442330ea4333e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Everyone in my family looks up ………………… my grandfather.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "to",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "44ffe0a46b174692a9a56ab1a97ea43d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The rope gave …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "way",
                "away",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "feacb02a3d77457893b719e8422aaaec"
        },
        {
            "question": "We will not put ………………. with such an insult.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "up",
                "away"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9460c55e2c3c4734b9b8b07208f6ba8e"
        }
    ]
}